A Guide to the Plats and certificates of the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1982
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Plats and certificates of the Virginia Land Office 1779-1982.
The Library of Virginia
LOI 42
96 cu. ft.
Virginia Land Office
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
No acquisition information available. Acquired prior to 1905.
Historical Information
The act that established the Land Office in 1779, provided for a Register to be at the head, who would be "appointed from time to time, by joint ballot of both houses of assembly...." It was the responsibility of the Register to carry out the very carefully structured legislation which provided the procedure for obtaining waste and unappropriated lands. So thorough was the system that no major change in Virginia's method of distribution of virgin land was made until the mid-20th century.
Under the act, any person could purchase as much vacant land as desired upon payment to the treasurer of a fee of £40 for 100 acres desired. The receipt given in return for the fee was taken to the auditor of the commonwealth. For this treasurer's receipt the auditor issued a certificate noting the amount of land to which the person was entitled. This certificate was taken to the Land Office where the Register issued a warrant. This warrant authorized any surveyor to lay off the quantity of land.
The warrantee entered a claim to the land he desired by depositing his warrant with the surveyor of the county in which the land lay. The act specified the method to be employed by the surveyor in returning his survey of the land. Once the survey had been completed, it and the depleted warrant on which it was based were returned to the warrantee whose responsibility it was to deliver the paper to the Land Office. There, all papers were examined initially for technical error and, if correctly executed, were filed for a period of not less than six months. If, within that time, no caveat was entered on the survey, the plat and certificate of survey were recorded and the grant was issued by the Register. Once written, the grant was signed by the governor, sealed, recorded, and delivered to the grantee.
During the first years of operation, the Land Office was mainly concerned with issuing warrants for military bounty, and satisfying claims originating under the colonial government. Since much of the available land was located in Kentucky, the Register was authorized in November, 1781, to appoint a deputy who would locate his office there.
Following the reorganization of the Land Office, recited in the Virginia Code of 1850, the localities were charged with the responsibilities of issuing titles to vacant lands, while the state issued grants for escheated lands only. To counter dissatisfaction with the existence of the Land Office, which first surfaced mid-19th century as the amount of wasteland declined, the General Assembly adopted the solution of assigning more duties to the Register. First, the office of Superintendent of Weights and Measures was abolished by an act of February 9, 1867, and his duties were transferred to the Register. Then, by an act of February 28, 1874, amended April 29, 1874, the responsibilities of the Superintendent of Public Buildings were assigned to the Register, and the former position was abolished. Next, in March, 1875, the Register was made the Secretary of the Board of Immigration.
Finally by legislative action of March 20, 1924, it was decreed that when the next vacancy in the position of Register of the Land Office occurred, that office was to be abolished and its duties transferred to the Secretary of the Commonwealth. The duties of Superintendent of Buildings and Grounds, performed by the Register, were to be taken over by the Superintendent of State Office Buildings, who would assume the former title. This transfer of duties was accomplished by January 1925.
In 1948 the records of the Land Office which were in the custody of the Secretary of the Commonwealth were transferred to the State Library and, by Act of Assembly, March 5, 1952, the duties of the Register of the Land Office were transferred from the Secretary of the Commonwealth to the State Librarian.
Scope and Content
These records contain plats/surveys, certificates of survey and other accompanying papers on which grants were issued through the register of the Land Office between 1779 and 1924, the secretary of the commonwealth between 1925 and 1948, and the state librarian since 1949. Supplemental papers may include warrants, assignments, affidavits, and copies of county court records.
These records are arranged chronologically by the year the land grant was issued. Within each year, the files are arranged alphabetically.
Included are land grants from numerous Virginia governors including: Patrick Henry (1776-1779; 1784-1786), Thomas Jefferson (1779-1781), Edmund Randolph (1786-1788), Beverley Randolph (1788-1791), Henry Lee (1791-1794), Robert Brooke (1794-1796), James Wood (1796-1799), and James Monroe (1799-1802, 1811). Also included are land patents from King George II (1683-1760) and King George III (1738-1820) of Great Britain. Most of these are housed in oversize boxes with separation notices.
These records are currently being rehoused. All years (1779-1982) are available, however only the rehoused records are listed in this finding aid.
Contents List
- 1779
  - A, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - B, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - C, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - D, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - E, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - F, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - G, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ha, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - He-Hi, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ho-Hu, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - J, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - K, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - L, 1779. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - M, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - N-O, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - P, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - William Preston and William Campbell, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - William Preston and William Thompson, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - R, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sh-Sp, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - St-Sw, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - T, 1779. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - V, 1779. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Wa-Will, 1779. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Wils-Wr, 1779. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Y, 1779. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 1780
  - Aa-Ak, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Al-Ar, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - As-Ay, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ba, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Be, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bi-Bl, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bo, 1780. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bra-Bro, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bru-Bu, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cab-Cam, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Can-Chi, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cho-Cla, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cle-Col, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Com-Cox, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cra-Cur, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Da, 1780. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - De, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Di, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Do, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dr-Du, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ea-Ec, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ed-El, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eu-Ew, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fa-Fi, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fl-Ford, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Forg-Fu, 1780. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Ga-Ge, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gi, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gl-Go, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gr-Gw, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gac-Hai, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hal-Harg, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Haro-Harv, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gat-Hay, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - He, 1780. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hi, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ho, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hub-Hun, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hur-Hut, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - I, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ja-Ji, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Johnston, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jones-Ju, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ka-Ke, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ki, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - La, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Le, 1780. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Li-Log, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lom-Ly, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mc, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mab-Mas, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mat-May, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Me-Mi, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Mo-Mu, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Na, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ne, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Ni-Nu, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 9a)
  - Oa-Og, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ol-Ow, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Pag-Pas, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Pat, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Pax-Pay, 1780. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ped-Per, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pet-Pi, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Po, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pr-Pu, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Q-Rag, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ram-Ran, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Re, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ri, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Roa-Rob, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rod-Row, 1780. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ru, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sa-Se, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Sh, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Si-Sme, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Smith, A-H, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Smith, J-W, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sn-Sp, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sta, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ste, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Sti-Sto, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Str-Sy, 1780. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - S (miscellaneous loose items), 1780. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Tal, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tan-Tay, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Te, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Thom, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Thor-Ti, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - To-Tr, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tu-Ty, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - V, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Wa-Wall, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Walt-Wat, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ward, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - We, 1780. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Wilc-Will, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Wils-Wit, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Wh, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Wo, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Wr-Wy, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Y-Z, 1780. (Box 12, Folder 6)
- 1781
  - Ac-Am, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - An-Ay, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ba, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Be, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bi-Bo, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bra-Bro, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bru-By, 1781. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Ca, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ch-Ci, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cl-Co, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cr-Cu, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Da, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - De-Dic, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dil-Diy, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Do-Dy, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - E, 1781. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fa-Fi, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Fl-Fu, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Ga, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gi-Go, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gra, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gri-Gu, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Had-Han, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Harb-Harr, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hars-Hay, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - He, 1781. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hi, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hoa-Hod, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hol-Hou, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Hu, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - I, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ja-Johnson, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Johnston-Ju, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ke, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ki, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - La, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Le-Ly, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ma, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Mc, 1781. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Me-Mi, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mo-Mu, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Na, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Ne-Nu, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - O, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Par, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pat, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pau-Pay, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pe-Pi, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Poa-Pol, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Poo-Pu, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ra, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Re, 1781. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Rh-Ri, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Roa-Rod, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rog-Ru, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Se, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Sh, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sl, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sm, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Sn-Sti, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Sto-Sy, 1781. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Ta-Te, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Th-To, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Tr-Tu, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - V, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wad-Wag, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wal, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - War-Wat, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - We, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Wh-Wil, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Wim-Wr, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Y, 1781. (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 1782
  - A, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ba, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Be, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bi, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Bl-Bu, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ca, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Ch-Coo, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cor-Cu, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - D, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - E, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - F, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ga-Gi, 1782. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Go-Gr, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Ha, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - He-Ho, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - I, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - J, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - K, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - L, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Ma, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mc, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Me-Mi, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Mo-Mu, 1782. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - N, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - O, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Pa-Ph, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Po-Pu, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - R, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Sc-Sm, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - St-Sy, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ta-Te, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Th-Tu, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - V, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Wal, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - War-Wau, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - We, 1782. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Wh, 1782. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Wi, 1782. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Wo, 1782. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Wr, 1782. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- 1783
  - A, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Be, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bi-Bl, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Br, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Bu-By, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Ca, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ch, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Cl, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Co, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Cr-Cu, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Da, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - De-Di, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Do-Du, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Ea-Ep, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Ev-Ew, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - F, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ga, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Gi-Gl, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Go-Gw, 1783. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Had-Han, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hap-Hay, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - He, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Hi-Ho, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Hu, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - I, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - J, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - La-Le, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Li-Ly, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Mab-Mar, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mas-May, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - McCa-McCl, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - McMc-McP, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mi-Mo, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - N, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - O, 1783. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Pa-Pi, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Pl-Po, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Pr-Pu, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ra-Rol, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ron-Ru, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Sh, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Si-Sl, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Sm-Sta, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ste, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Sti-Su, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ta, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Te-Th, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - T-Tr, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - V, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Wa, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - We-Wh, 1783. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Wi, 1783. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - W0-Wr, 1783. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Y, 1783. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- 1784
  - A-Ad, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Al, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Am-An, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Ap-Ay, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Bac-Bal, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ban-Bay, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Banks, Henry, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bea-Ber, 1784. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Bi-Bo, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Br, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bu-By, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ca-Calhoon, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Call-Can, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Car-Ce, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cha-Che, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Chi-Chr, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Ci-Cl, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Coa-Cog, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Col-Col, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Coo-Cox, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Cr-Cu, 1784. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Da-Davis, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Davison-Day, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - De, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Di-Do, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Du, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - E, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Fa-Fl, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fo-Fu, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Ga-Go, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Gr-Gu, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Had-Hal, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Ham-Hap, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Har-Hay, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - He-Hi, 1784. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Ho, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Hu, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - I, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ja-Johnson, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Johnston-Jones, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ju, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - K, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - La, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Le, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Li-Ly, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - McCakey-McCollough, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - McCutchan-McWilliams, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Ma, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Me-Mi, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mo, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Mu, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - N, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - O, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Pa, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Pe, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ph-Po, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Pr-Pu, 1784. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Q, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Ra-Re, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Ri-Rob, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Rod-Row, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Ru-Ry, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sc-Shel, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Shep-Sla, 1784. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sm, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Sn-Ste, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sti-Sw, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Ta-Te, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Th-Ti, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - To-Tr, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Tu-Ty, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - V, 1784. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Wad-Was, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Wat, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - We-Wh, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Wic-Wilm, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Wim-Wit, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Wol-Woo, 1784. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Wor-Wy, 1784. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Y, 1784. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Z, 1784. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- 1785
  - Ac-Ad, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ak-Al, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - An-Au, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Ba-Barn, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Barr-Bax, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Henry, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Be, 1785. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Bi, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Bl, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Bo, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Bra-Bri, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Bro-Bry, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Buc-Burg, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Burk-By, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Cab-Cal, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Campbell, 1785. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Cam-Caz, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ce-Cha, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Che-Ci, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Cl, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Claiborne, Richard, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Claiborne, Richard, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Cle-Clo, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Coc-Coh, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Col-Cop, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Cor-Cox, 1785. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Cra-Cre, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Cri-Cro, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Cru-Cy, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Da-Davidson, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Davies, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Davies, William, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Davis-Davison, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - De, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Deakins, 1785. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Di, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Do-Dr, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Du-Dy, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Ea-Ec, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Ed, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - El-Er, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Et-Ev, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Ew, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Fa, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Fe-Fi, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Fl, 1785. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Fo, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fowler, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Fr, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Fu, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Ga-Ge, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Gh-Gi, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Gibbs, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Gl-Gof, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Goo-Gor, 1785. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Gra-Grea, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Gree-Gro, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Had-Han, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Hanway, Samual, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Harb-Harp, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Harr-Harv, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Hat-Hay, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - He, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Hi, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Hob-Hol, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 1-20), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 22, 24, 49-52), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 74-79, 85-86), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 104-118), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 123-139), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 146, 148, 150, 152), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 154-164), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 187-199), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 200-214), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 215-229), 1785. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 230-242), 1785. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Hollingsworth, Levi; Grats, Barnard; Grats, Michael; Penticost, Dorsey; Willing, Charles; Wilson, James (No. 324-333), 1785. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hoo-Hos, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Hov-How, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Hu-Hy, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - I, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Ja-Ji, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Johnston, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Johnston, Benjamin, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Jo-Ju, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Ka-Ke, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Kin, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Kir-Kit, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ko-Ky, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - La-Lea, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Led-Lep, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lew, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Li-Log, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Lou-Ly, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Ma, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Martin, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - McA-McCl, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - McCo-McCu, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - McD, 1785. (Box 48, Folder 8)